A Finding Aid to the Lorence-Monk Gallery Records, 1961-1992, in the Archives of American Art AAA.loremong
Archives of American Art
Lorence-Monk Gallery records
1961-1992
AAA.loremong
Archives of American Art
3.4 Linear feet
The records of Lorence-Monk Gallery measure normal="1957"> and scrapbooks documenting approximately ninety exhibitions and over 250 American and European artists represented by the gallery from its opening in 1985 until it closed its operation in 1992.
Lorence-Monk Gallery
Historical Note
The Lorence-Monk Gallery, founded in 1985 by Susan Lorence and Robert Monk was located at 568-578 Broadway, in the SoHo section of New York City. Prior to establishing the gallery, Susan Lorence was the American Director of the Petersburg Press and Robert Monk was the Director of Castelli Graphics.
The Lorence-Monk Gallery promoted the work of contemporary and emerging artists, featuring a diverse selection of paintings, prints, sculptures, and photographs. The gallery held rotating exhibits organized by theme, individual artists, and group shows. Among the younger generation of artists represented by the gallery were: John Beerman, Jasper Johns, Jürgen Partenheimer, Alan Saret, Carole Seborovski, Alan Uglow, and Günter Umberg.
Beginning with its inaugural show "A Print Survey, 1960-1985," the Lorence-Monk Gallery became a major venue for the graphic arts, including lithographs, etchings, screenprints, and woodcuts. Exhibitions featured the work of prominent artists, many who had worked in other media, such as Richard Artschwager, David Hockney, Jasper Johns, Bruce Nauman, and Barnett Newman.
The gallery's exhibitions included sculpture and object installations, offering the works of Kim Jones, Laurie Parsons, Ursula von Rydingsvard, Sandy Skoglund, and others. The Lorence-Monk Gallery promoted independent publishers of prints, portfolios, and books, including Peter Blum Editions, Diane Villani Editions, and the Universal Limited Art Editions (ULAE). Several exhibitions were organized by independent curators, such as Marvin Heiferman, Clarissa Dalyrymple, and Christopher Sweet. Also there were exhibitions held in conjunction with other galleries, including Leo Castelli Graphics, Jim Kempner Fine Art, and the Robert Miller Gallery.
The gallery closed in 1992. Susan Lorence continues to work as a New York-based independent dealer. Robert Monk is Director at the Gagosian Gallery in New York City.
Scope and Content Note
The records of Lorence-Monk Gallery measure 3.4 linear feet and date from 1961-1992. The collection consists of exhibition files and scrapbooks documenting approximately ninety exhibitions and over 250 American and European artists represented by the Lorence-Monk Gallery from its opening in 1985 until it closed its operation in 1992.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 2 series:
Series 1: Exhibition Files, 1961-1991 (Boxes 1-3; 2.2 linear feet)
Series 2: Exhibition Scrapbooks, 1985-1992 (Boxes 3-4; 1.2 linear feet)
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Lorence-Monk Gallery Records were donated by Susan Lorence and Robert Monk in 2002.
Restrictions on Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment.
Lorence, Susan; Monk, Robert; Art galleries, Commercial--New York (State)--New York; Art, Modern--20th century; Scrapbooks
- Exhibition Files, 1961-1991; Series 1; 2.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-3
  Scope and Contents note
  This series documents approximately ninety exhibitions organized and jointly sponsored by the Lorence-Monk Gallery. Files include annotated checklists, price lists, consignments, loan agreements; the materials provide an overview of the gallery's daily operations and business dealings with artists and dealers. Also included are curriculum vitae, artists' statements, press releases, reviews, transcripts of interviews and notes that chronicle the gallery's promotion of contemporary and emerging artists, many who have since become part of the established art scene.
  Files include photographs of installations and artwork. Exhibitions were limited runs of a few weeks; the installation shots provide a rich visual resource of the contemporary work advanced by the gallery. There are some photographs of artists. Also found are slides of artwork.
  Arrangement note
  Exhibition files are arranged in chronological order. Miscellaneous photographs are located at the end of the exhibition files.
  - "A Print Survey: 1960-1985" (1985 January 30-February 23) (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - "Jürgen Partenheimer" (1985 March 2-March 30) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Drawings" (1985 April 4-April 27), 1984-1985; undated (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
  - "Real Surreal" (1985 May 4-May 25), 1984-1985; undated (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
  - "Peter Blum Edition, Recent Publications" (1985 May 30-June 29), 1985-1986; undated (Box 1, Folder 10-14)
  - "Jasper Johns, The Screenprints, 1968-1982" (1985 July 9-August 23) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Jasper Johns/Samuel Beckett, Foirades/Fizzles" (1985 September 14-October 5), 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Alan Uglow, Sign and Other Paintings" (1985 October 19-November 16), undated; 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - "Group Exhibition: John Beerman, Edward Henderson, Alan Herman, Dennis Kardon, and Karla Knight" (1985 November 23-December 21), undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Group Exhibition: Nancy Haynes, Joseph Marioni, Gordon Moore, Günter Umberg, and Michael Young" (1986 January 11-February 8), undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Print Review, 1983-1985" (1986 February 15-March 8), undated (Box 1, Folder 21-24)
  - "Drawings: Ernst Caramelle, Robert Cumming, Edward Henderson, Shoici Ida, Linda Karshan, and Jürgen Partenheimer" (1986 March 15-April 5), 1985-1987; undated (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
  - "Edward Henderson" (1986 April 12-May 10) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "European Drawings" (1986 May 17-June 7), undated (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
  - "Painting the Object" (1986 June 14-July 26), undated; 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
  - "Paintings and Drawings" (1986 September 20-October 11) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Michael Young" (1986 October 18-November 15) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "The Manor in the Landscape" (1986 November 22-December 20), 1986-1990; undated (Box 1, Folder 34-37)
  - "Group Exhibition: Judy Fiskin, Brian Gayman, Kim Jones, Paul Laster, Paul Mogensen, and Laurie Parsons" (1987 January 10-January 31) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "Ron Janowich, Monotypes from the Garner Tullis Workshop, Santa Barbara" (1987 February 7-February 28), 1986-1988; undated (Box 1, Folder 39-41)
  - "Günter Umberg" (1987 March 7-March 28), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - "John Beerman, Paintings" (1987 April 4-April 25), undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - "Jürgen Partenheimer, Paintings and Works on Paper" (1987 May 2-May 30), undated (Box 1, Folder 44-45)
  - "Art Against AIDS, Benefit Exhibition and Sale" (1987 June 4), undated; 1973-1988 (Box 1, Folder 46-56)
  - "Paintings: John Beerman, Edward Henderson, Ron Janowich, Karla Knight, Stefan Kürten, Joseph Marioni, Paul Mogensen, Carole Seborovski, Alan Uglow, Günter Umberg, and Michael Young" (1987 July 7-July 31) (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - "Peter Blum Edition: Enzo Cucchi, General Idea, Brice Marden, and James Turrell" (1987 September 19-October 10), 1987-1991; undated (Box 1, Folder 58-59)
  - "Karla Knight" (1987 October 17-November 7) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - "John Duff, Robert Lobe, and Al Taylor" (1987 November 14-December 5), 1983-1987; undated (Box 1, Folder 61-64)
  - "Jasper Johns, Lead Reliefs" (1987 December 12-1988 January 9), undated; 1969-1988 (Box 1, Folder 65-68)
  - "Alan Uglow, Signals, An Installation" (1988 January 16-February 6), undated (Box 1, Folder 69-70)
  - "Carole Seborovski" (1988 February 13-March 5), undated, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 71-75)
  - "Joseph Marioni" (1988 March 12-April 2), undated; 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - "Kim Jones, Sculpture" (1988 April 9-April 30), undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - "Laurie Parsons" (1988 May 7-May 28) (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - "Life Like" (1988 June 4-June 25), 1981-1989; undated (Box 1, Folder 79-84)
  - "Objects" (1988 July 7-July 29) (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - "Sandy Skoglund" (1988 September 17-October 15) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Al Taylor" (1988 October 22-November 12), 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Alan Uglow" (1988 November 19-December 22) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Paintings and Works on Paper: Suzan Frecon, Joseph Marioni, Paul Mogensen, Carole Seborovski, and Alan Uglow" (1989 January 7-January 28), undated; 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10-13)
  - "Drawings" (1989 February 4-February 28), 1976-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - "Universal Limited Art Editions (ULAE), 1982-1989" (1989 March 4-March 25), undated (Box 2, Folder 16-19)
  - "Alan Saret, Angle and Axis" (1989 April 1-April 22), 1988-1990; undated (Box 2, Folder 20-24)
  - "Painting Show: Steve Di Benedetto, Gary Hume, Julian Lethbridge, Nicolas Rule, and Matthew Weinstein" (1989 April 29-May 26), 1986-1990; undated (Box 2, Folder 25-27)
  - "Günter Umberg" (1989 May 6-June 3), undated (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
  - "Pop Prints" (1989 June 3-June 30) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "Minimal Prints" (1989 July 11- July 28) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Summer Group Exhibition" (1989 June 10-July 28) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - "Lewis Baltz, The New Industrial Parks near Irvine, California" (1989 September 16-October 14), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - "Bruce Nauman, A Print Retrospective in Conjunction with Castelli Graphics" (1989 September 16-October 14), 1970-1991 (Box 2, Folder 34-38)
  - "Jasper Johns, Etchings, 1967-1989" (1989 October 21-November 11), undated (Box 2, Folder 39-42)
  - "Carole Seborovski" (1989 October 21-November 11) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - "John Beerman, Paintings, New Mexico" (1989 November 18-December 16) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - "Peter Blum Edition: John Baldessari, Louise Bourgeois, Helmut Federale, Eric Fischl, Alex Katz, Sherrie Levine, James Turrell, and Terry Winters" (1989 November 18-December 16), undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - "Kim Jones" (1990 January 6-January 27), undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - "Robert Rauschenberg Prints in Association with Jim Kempner Fine Art" (1990 January 6-January 27), undated; 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - "David Hockney, Prints from the Sixties and Seventies" (1990 February 3-February 24) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - "The Indomitable Spirit, Photographers and Friends United Against AIDS" (1990 February 3-February 24), undated; 1979-1990 (Box 2, Folder 49-50)
  - "Karla Knight" (1990 February 3-February 24), undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - "Donald Lipski" (1990 February 3-February 24), undated; 1981-1990 (Box 2, Folder 52-56)
  - "Ursula von Rydingsvard" (1990 March 3-March 31), undated; 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 57-59)
  - "Dimitry Merinoff" (1990 April 7-April 28), undated; 1961-1990 (Box 2, Folder 60-62)
  - "Ted Stamm" (1990 April 7-April 28) (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - "Barnett Newman, Etchings and Lithographs" (1990 May), undated; 1968-1990 (Box 2, Folder 64-66)
  - "Laurie Parsons" (1990 May), undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - "Richard Artschwager/Joseph Beuys, Prints and Multiples" (1990 June 2-June 23), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - "Drawings: Joseph Amar, Richard Artschwager, Kim Jones, Joseph Marioni, Bruce Nauman, and Edward Ruscha" (1990 June 2-June 23) (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - "Joyce Kozloff, Patterns of Desire" (1990 June 2-June 23), 1979-1991; undated (Box 2, Folder 70-72)
  - "Selected Prints" (1990 July 5-July 28) (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - "Summer Group Exhibition" (1990 July 5-August 24), 1989-1990; undated (Box 2, Folder 74-75)
  - "Selected Prints" (1990 September-October) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Joseph Amar" (1990 September 22-October 13) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Alan Uglow" (1990 October 20-November 10) (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
  - "Diane Villani Editions: Gregory Amenoff, Mel Bochner, Richard Bosman, Louisa Chase, Joan Snyder, and Michelle Stuart" (1990 October 20-November 10), undated; 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6-8)
  - "Al Taylor" (1990 November 17-December 8) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "John Beerman, Etchings and Monotypes from Hudson River Editions" (1990 November 17-December 22) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "Children in Crisis, A Benefit Exhibition" (1991 January 12-February 2), undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Dead Heroes, Disfigured Love" (1991 February 2-February 23), undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "Kim Jones, Mens Room" (1991 March 2-March 30) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Drawings" (1991 April 6-May 11), undated; 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - "Black and White Prints" (1991 April 6-May 11) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "Brian Weil" (1991 May 18-June 29), undated (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
  - "In a Dream, A Limited Edition Portfolio, Photographers and Friends United Against AIDS" (1991 May 18-June 29) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Berenice Abbott" (1991 May 28-June 29) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "Summer Group Exhibition" (1991 July 9-July 27), undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs of Artwork, 1991; undated (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
- Exhibition Scrapbooks, 1985-1992; Series 2; 1.1 Linear feet Boxes 3-4
  Exhibition scrapbooks contain curriculum vitate, exhibition announcements, checklists, printed material, clippings, press releases, and photographs of exhibition installations and artwork. The scrapbooks document the gallery's exhibitions during its seven years in business.
  Much of the materials in the scrapbooks can be found in Series 1: Exhibtions Files. Also scrapbooks include exhibitions not found in Series 1: Exhibition Files.
  Exhibition scrapbooks were received in eight binders. The processor disbound the material and filed the items within folders, retaining the original order that they were received. Files are arranged in chronological order.
  - "A Print Survey, 1960-1985" (1985 January 30-February 23) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "Jürgen Partenheimer" (1985 March 2-March 30) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Drawings" (1985 April 4-April 27) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "Real Surreal" (1985 May 4-May 25) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "Peter Blum Edition, Recent Publications" (1985 May 30-June 29) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "Jasper Johns, The Screenprints, 1968-1982" (1985 July 9-August 23) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Jasper Johns/Samuel Beckett, Foirades/Fizzles" (1985 September 14-October 5) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Alan Uglow, Sign and Other Paintings" (1985 October 19-November 16) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Group Exhibition: John Beerman, Edward Henderson, Alan Herman, Dennis Kardon, and Karla Knight" (1985 November 23-December 21) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "Group Exhibition: Nancy Haynes, Joseph Marioni, Gordon Moore, Günter Umberg, and Michael Young" (1986 January 11-February 8) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - "Print Review, 1983-1985" (1986 February 15-March 8) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - "Drawings: Ernst Caramelle, Robert Cumming, Edward Henderson, Shoici Ida, Linda Karshan, and Jürgen Partenheimer" (1986 March 15-April 5) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - "Edward Henderson" (1986 April 12-May 10) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - "European Drawings" (1986 May 17-June 7) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - "Painting the Object" (1986 June 14-July 26) (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - "Paintings and Drawings" (1986 September 20-October 11) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - "Michael Young" (October 18-November 15), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - "The Manor in the Landscape" (1986 November 22-December 20) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - "Group Exhibition: Judy Fiskin, Brian Gayman, Kim Jones, Paul Laster, Paul Mogensen, and Laurie Parsons" (1987 January 10-January 31) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - "Ron Janowich, Monotypes from the Garner Tullis Workshop, Santa Barbara" (1987 February 7-February 28) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - "Günter Umberg" (1987 March 7-March 28) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - "John Beerman, Paintings" (1987 April 4-April 25) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - "Jürgen Partenheimer, Paintings and Works on Paper" (1987 May 2-May 30) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - "Art Against AIDS, Benefit Exhibition and Sale" (1987 June 4) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - "Paintings: John Beerman, Edward Henderson, Ron Janowich, Karla Knight, Stefan Kürten, Joseph Marioni, Paul Mogensen, Carole Seborovski, Alan Uglow, Günter Umberg, and Michael Young" (1987 July 7-July 31) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - "Peter Blum Edition: Enzo Cucchi, General Idea, Brice Marden, and James Turrell" (1987 September 19-October 10) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - "Karla Knight" (1987 October 17-November 7) (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - "John Duff, Robert Lobe, and Al Taylor" (1987 November 14-December 5) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - "Jasper Johns, Lead Reliefs" (1987 December 12-1988 January 9), 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - "Alan Uglow, Signals, An Installation" (1988 January 16-February 6) (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - "Carole Seborovski" (1988 February 13-March 5) (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - "Joseph Marioni" (1988 March 12-April 2) (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - "Kim Jones, Sculpture" (1988 April 9-April 30) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - "Laurie Parsons" (1988 May 7-May 28) (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - "Life Like" (1988 June 4-June 25) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - "Objects" (1988 July 7-July 29) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - "Sandy Skoglund" (1988 September 17-October 15) (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - "Al Taylor" (1988 October 22-November 12, 1988) (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - "Alan Uglow" (1988 November 19-December 22) (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - "Paintings and Works on Paper: Suzan Frecon, Joseph Marioni, Paul Mogensen, Carole Seborovski, and Alan Uglow" (1989 January 7-January 28) (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - "Drawings" (1989 February 4-February 25) (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - "Universal Limited Art Editions (ULAE), 1982-1989" (1989 March 4-March 25) (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - "Alan Saret, Angle and Axis" (1989 April 1-April 22) (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - "Painting Show: Steve Di Benedetto, Gary Hume, Julian Lethbridge, Nicolas Rule, and Matthew Weinstein" (1989 April 29-May 26) (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - "Günter Umberg" (1989 May 6-June 3) (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - "Pop Prints" (1989 June 3-June 30) (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - "Minimal Prints"(1989 July 11-July 28) (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - "Summer Group Exhibition" (1989 June 10-July 28) (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - "Lewis Baltz, The New Industrial Parks near Irvine, California" (1989 September 16-October 14) (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - "Bruce Nauman, A Print Retrospective in Conjunction with Castelli Graphics" (1989 September 16-October 14) (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - "Jasper Johns, Etchings, 1967-1989" (1989 October 21-November 11) (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - "Carole Seborovksi" (1989 October 21-November 11) (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - "John Beerman, Paintings, New Mexico" (1989 November 18-December 16) (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - "Peter Blum Edition, John Baldesarri, Louise Bourgeois, Helmut Federale, Eric Fischl, Alex Katz, Sherrie Levine, James Turrell, and Terry Winters" (1989 November 18-December 16) (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - "Kim Jones" (1990 January 6-January 27) (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - "Robert Rauschenberg Prints in Association with Jim Kempner Fine Art" (1990 January 6-January 27) (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - "David Hockney, Prints from the Sixties and Seventies" (1990 February 3-February 24) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Karla Knight, and The Indomitable Spirit, Photographers and Friends United Against Aids, and "Donald Lipski" (1990 February 3-February 24) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Ursula von Rydingsvard" (1990 March 3-March 31) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "Dimitry Merinoff" (1990 April 7-April 28) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "Ted Stamm" (1990 April 7-April 28) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Barnett Newman, Etchings and Lithographs" (1990 May) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Laurie Parsons" (1990 May) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Richard Artschwager and Joseph Beuys, Prints and Multiples" (1990 June 2-June 23) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Drawings: Joseph Amar, Richard Artschwager, Kim Jones, Joseph Marioni, Bruce Nauman, and Edward Ruscha" (1990 June 2-June 23), and "Joyce Kozloff, Patterns of Desire" (1990 June 2-June 23) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Selected Prints" (1990 July 5 - July 28), and "Summer Group Exhibition" (1990 July 5-August 24) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Joseph Amar" (1990 September 22-October 13) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "Alan Uglow" (1990 October 20-November 10) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Diane Villani Editions: Gregory Amenoff, Mel Bochner, Richard Bosman, Louisa Chase, Joan Snyder, and Michelle Stuart" (1990 October 20-November 10) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "Al Taylor" (1990 November 17-December 8) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "John Beerman, Etchings and Monotypes from Hudson River Editions" (1990 November 17-December 22) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Alan Scarritt, Glyphs, Cuts, and Troll" (1990 December 15-1991 January 26) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "Dead Heroes, Disfigured Love" (1991 February 2-February 23) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Artists' Books" (1991 February 9-March 23) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Kim Jones, Mens Room" (1991 March 2-March 30) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - "Drawings" (1991 April 6-May 11) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "Black and White Prints" (1991 April 6-May 18) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - "Brian Weil" and "In A Dream, A Limited Edition Portfolio, Photographers and Friends United Against Aids" (1991 May 18-June 29) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "Berenice Abbott" (1991 May 28-June 29) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Summer Group Exhibition" (1991 July 9-July 26) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - "Ursula Von Rydingsvard" (1991 September 14-October 26) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - "Günter Förg, Edition Julie Sylvester" (1991 October 12-November 30) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - "John Beerman, The Sound of Trees" (1991 November 9-December 21) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - "Group Exhibition" (1992 January 14-February 1) (Box 4, Folder 28)